listenarabic.com 2018-05-27

# Privacy Policy - Download FREE Arabic Songs Radio App ListenArabic.com

### Get to know more about ListenArabic.com Privacy policy.

**ListenArabic.com Privacy policy  **

 **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you access the pages in the app. 

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

 **Do we use cookies?**

We do not use cookies.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.listenarabic.com/dmca-policy/

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

<http://www.listenarabic.com/>  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
